extremerestraints.com 2019-12-02

# Privacy Policy | Information Usage and Customer Account Preferences

At XR. LLC, we respect the privacy of all visitors who access and use our corporate Web site. The information we collect on this site is used to understand how we can enhance our site and improve your experience. This policy describes the limited circumstances in which we collect personal information, why we collect it and how we use it. Our policy also describes the choices you can make about how we collect and use your information

If our information practices change in the future, we will post an updated policy on this Web site. You can tell if the policy has changed by checking the revision date that appears below.

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please contact us at info@xrllc.com.

**What kind of information does XR. LLC. collect?**  
We may collect personal information from you, such as your name, email address, postal address, phone number, etc., when you visit our website, or contact us with a question or concern.

**How does XR. LLC use my information?**  
We may use your personal information in the following ways:

• To communicate with you, and to send you information by email (and or other means) about our company  
• To help us address problems with and improve our site design, products and services  
• To analyze trends and statistics  
• To protect the security or integrity of our websites and our business  
• To contact you if necessary

You always have the choice not to receive information or communications from us. For instructions on opting out, please see the section entitled, "How do I make choices about receiving promotional communications?", below.

**Does XR. LLC share my information?**  
We do not sell or rent the information you provide to us to third parties. However, we do contract with service providers to assist us in maintaining and managing our databases and to communicate with those who are interested in our company. We do not authorize any of those third parties to make any other use of your information. Additionally, we may disclose and maintain user information in special cases, including:

• In the unlikely event of a sale of some or all of our business, we will disclose your personal information to a purchaser that agrees to abide by the terms and conditions of this privacy policy  
• If necessary, in our good faith judgment, to comply with laws or regulations or in response to a valid subpoena, order, or government request, or to protect the rights of XR.LLC or others.

**How do I access or change my information?**

You can ask us to update your personal information by contacting us as described in the section entitled, "How do I contact you?", below. Please note that any request to update your personal information may take up to 10 days for your email request and 6-8 weeks for your postal mail request or Logging into user account settings and updating your account.

**How do I make choices about receiving promotional communications?**  
XR. LLC. wants to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. If you prefer not to receive promotional information or other communications from us, you can let us know by contacting our customer service as described in the section entitled, "How do I contact you?", below.

If you ask us to remove your name and address from promotional lists, we will maintain your name in a "do not contact" file to ensure that we can honor your request. It may take up to 10 days to process your email request and 6-8 weeks to process your postal mail request, during which period you may continue to receive communications from us. You can also opt out of newsletters by clicking the opt out link on any promotional email.

**How does XR. LLC use cookies?**  
We make limited use of cookies on this Web site. A cookie is a small data file that Web sites often store on your computer's hard drive when you visit their sites. A cookie may contain information (such as a unique user ID) that is used to track the pages of the sites you've visited. We use cookies for the limited purpose of determining whether you have visited a particular page before, so that you will not have to view introductory information that is played for first-time visitors. We do not store personally identifiable information in your cookie.

**Website Analytics**  
We may also partner with selected third-party vendors, such as Google Analytics, to allow tracking technologies and remarketing services on the Site through the use of first party cookies and third-party cookies, to, among other things, analyze and track users’ use of the Site, to determine the popularity of certain content and better understand online activity. By accessing the Site, you consent to the collection and use of your information by these third-party vendors. You are encouraged to review their privacy policy and contact them directly for responses to your questions. We do not transfer personal information to these third-party vendors. However, If you do not want any information to be collected and used by tracking technologies, you can visit the third-party vendor or Digital Advertising Alliance Opt-Out Tool.

You should be aware that getting a new computer, installing a new browser, upgrading an existing browser, or erasing or otherwise altering your browser’s cookies files may also clear certain opt-out cookies, plug-ins, or settings.

**How do I know my personal information is secure?**  
We have in place certain physical, electronic, and managerial safeguards to protect the security and privacy of your personal information.

**What is "phishing"?**  
"Phishing" is a scam designed to steal your personal information. If you receive an email that looks like it is from us asking you for your personal information, do not respond. We will never request your password, user name, credit card information or other personal information through email.

**How do I contact you?**  
For questions about our privacy policy, to make choices about receiving promotional or other communications, or to update your personal information, you can contact us by email at info@xrllc.com or write to us at the address below.

**Your California Privacy Rights**  
California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits customers of XR. LLC. who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please write to us at the following address:

XR. LLC,15251 PIPELINE LANE, HUNTINGTON BEACH, CA 92649

Last edited 6/6/2018
